nuzzel.com 2018-10-21

# Nuzzel Privacy Policy

##  1\. Introduction

Thank you for visiting Nuzzel.com. This Privacy Policy, like our Terms of Service, is a fancy legal document that you have to agree to if you don't want our bouncers to show you the door.

##  2\. Definitions

Throughout this Privacy Policy, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand the meaning of them. The list is not all-encompassing and no definition should be considered binding to the point that it renders this Privacy Policy nonsensical:

"Nuzzel" refers to the business which owns this website (Nuzzel, Inc.), our Site, or our Service, depending on the context of the usage;

"Privacy Policy" means this Privacy Policy. Self-explanatory, really;

"Service" refers to the services that we provide through our Site, including but not limited to our social news reader service;

"Site" refers to our website, Nuzzel.com;

"User" refers to you and any other person who uses our Service, or visits our Site, whether they are a registered accountholder or not;

"You" refers to you, the person who is reading this Privacy Policy. Read our Terms of Service to know our advice for those who don't know what "you" means.

##  3\. Information Collected

Identifying Information Collected by Us

When using our website, you will interact with us using your Facebook and/or Twitter account through their APIs. Generally, we will at the minimum know your name and e-mail address. However, if you don't adjust your privacy settings a certain way, we may end up knowing your hobbies, favorite bands, and romantic secrets. Please adjust your Facebook and Twitter privacy settings accordingly.

If you enter your email address on our website in order to subscribe to a newsletter, we will know your email address, and may share it with newsletter curators.

Non-Identifying Information

Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, and Internet Service Provider. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you. Generally, unless you know a fortune teller or other clairvoyant, this information cannot be used to identify you without a subpoena.

##  4\. Use of Your Information

We may use your information:

  * To enhance or improve Users' experiences, our Site, or Service.
  * To send e-mails about our Site or respond to inquiries.
  * To send e-mails about the Site and other products, news, or updates for Nuzzel, or other businesses, websites, or services owned or operated by us.
  * To send newsletters, and to provide newsletter curators with a list of their subscribers

##  5\. Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information

Users may in some cases be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided to us by logging into their account on the Site and editing their account. Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser's cache. We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such. In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database. Also, we have no control over what Twitter or Facebook does with your information, and we can't stop people from saving things that you write or post.

You may unsubscribe from any Nuzzel newsletters by using the unsubscribe links at the bottom of these newsletters.

##  6\. Cookies

We use cookies to save your sessions and preferences. For this reason, you must have cookies enabled when you use our Site or Service. If you didn't enable cookies after we took the time to care what your preferences were, we'd think it awfully rude.

##  7\. Third Parties

Nuzzel or its Users may post links to third party websites on its Site or through its Service, which may include information that we have no control over. Whether you access third party websites through a link on our Site, or as a consequence of using our Service, you acknowledge that you are aware that these third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by us, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties. Nuzzel bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links or through our Service.

We use Facebook and/or Twitter to authenticate Users and associate them with a unique account. We may be given access to information in your Twitter and Facebook accounts that we would not otherwise have based on your privacy settings at those websites. We therefore repeat our recommendation that you adjust your Facebook and Twitter privacy settings accordingly, should you wish to limit the information made available to us.

##  8\. Third Party Access to Your Information

Throughout the course of our provision of our Services to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information. For example, our web host stores the information that you provide us, and we may hire third parties to assist us in maintaining, repairing, improving, or otherwise assisting us with our Site and Services.

It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy. For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

For greater certainty, and without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you agree that we may use and exchange information about you with Facebook and Twitter.

##  9\. Law Enforcement

You agree that we may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, NBC procedural crime drama, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you and release your information without receiving any request to third parties where we believe that it is proper to do so for legal reasons, such as instances where we believe your actions violate any law of the United States or any other country having jurisdiction over us, our Site, Services, or our Terms of Service. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants. We may release your information under the conditions listed in this paragraph whether it is to individuals or entities in the State of California, the rest of the United States, or elsewhere.

##  10\. Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications

By providing information to the Site that forms the basis of communication with you, such as contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email from us since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us or anyone else covered under this Privacy Policy. However, you may unsubscribe from our communications by notifying Nuzzel that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavour to remove you from our database where you have the right to request this under our Agreement, Privacy Policy, or applicable law, or where we voluntarily decide to grant the request. If you do this, you will make us sad, but we respect your decision.

You may opt-out of receiving further email from us by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of our email messages.

##  11\. Security Measures

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Services. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, routine credit checks, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security and privacy threats.

##  12\. Your California Privacy Rights

Nuzzel permits residents of the State of California to use its Service, and complies with the California Business and Professions Code Section 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at [info@nuzzel.com](mailto:info@nuzzel.com) with any questions.

##  13\. International Transfer

The Internet is a big place. Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside of the United States and choose to provide information to us, Nuzzel may transfer personal information to the United States or elsewhere and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

##  14\. Amendments

Like our Terms of Service, we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will update this page. You must agree to the amendments as a condition of your continued use of our Site and Service. If you do not agree, you must immediately cease using our Site and Service.

## To contact us:

Nuzzel, Inc.  
665 3rd St., Suite 150  
San Francisco, CA 94107  
415-358-8131  

Last Updated: May 18, 2016
